what's up everybody this is Nick at
bobbend.com and today I'm going to be
talking to you about the best whey
isolate protein powders on the market
protein powder number one selling Sports
Nutrition supplement you're going to get
at just about any supplement store whey
isolate is an extra nice like an elite
version of whey protein powder relative
to less expensive forms of whey protein
like whey concentrate way isolate has
fewer carbs and less fat which means
you're getting more protein per calorie
which means it's a more efficient way to
get your protein than we concentrate in
addition to that because it's so low in
carbohydrates it is frequently lactose
free and often a better a bet for
someone who has lactose sensitivities so
it's a really solid product and today
we're going to be talking about the best
way to isolates in several categories
including the best tasting weight
isolate the best all natural way to
isolate the best for weight loss and
more so stick around I'm going to teach
you all that way I slit and make you the
expert
before I keep going I need to make it
clear for all legal and ethical reasons
I am not a doctor I'm not a medical
professional and if you are planning to
make big changes or little changes to
your supplement regimen or your
nutrition regimen your diet your
exercise all of that and make absolutely
certainly speak to your own Medical
Professional to square everything away
and make sure that your selected Avenue
for self-improvement is consistent with
your own individual preferences
lifestyle medications and more talk to
your doctor before making changes to
your health regimen let's keep going
before I go on a little bit about the
science behind whey protein I did want
to just give you a break and tell you
what the top pick on this list is it's
wolverines wolverines way isolate is our
favorite pick four-way isolate for a few
reasons it's grass-fed so the cows spend
less time outside which is always nice
but it's also just got a lot of protein
per calorie so in one scoop of 110
calories you're just getting two grams
of carbohydrates and 0.5 grams of fat
for 26 grams of protein first of all
yeah what is whey protein what's
interesting about whey protein is that
it used to be considered a waste
byproduct so basically in milk there two
types of protein there's whey and
there's casing the casein that gets used
to make cheese the way it kind of you
just gets thrown out like because I
can't make cheese from it why do I want
it then someone figured out that you can
dry it out and make it into a protein
that is actually the most bioavailable
protein in the entire world that means
it absorbs the most effectively out of
any protein so it's just everybody's
go-to protein for protein powder if you
are someone who is happy to consume
dairy products that original way you get
when you dry out the Whey from the
teasing process that is way concentrate
all the different kinds of whey that's
the one with the most carbs and fat it's
also the least expensive now personally
I think if you make a whey constant
protein powder there's a better chance
it's going to taste good we have some
really good tasting ones here though but
because of the carbs and fats Some
people prefer it but because it doesn't
have as much protein per calorie a lot
of people prefer to get something that's
denser in protein and then you get whey
isolate which is the process in such a
way that it is lower in carbs and fat
and lactose so as I mentioned earlier
that can be better for folks lactose
sensitivities or just people who want
really low calorie diets and want to get
as much protein per calorie as possible
the third type of whey protein the last
one I'm going to mention here is whey
hydrolyset also called hydrolyzed whey
protein that is the most processed form
of way where the way isolate has been
further processed and broken down with
enzymes so that it has shorter peptide
chains so that it digests really really
quickly like among Olympic athletes if
they're working out twice per day they
might recover their power a little more
quickly when they take hydrolyzed away
between workouts than weight isolate
that sort of situation is really the
only one where hydralized way is worth
the extra money because it costs quite a
bit more money and if you're at an
extremely Elite level working out all
the time constantly multiple times per
day then probably a good idea to put the
extra expense into that otherwise even
if you work out every single day that
difference isn't going to be meaningful
and I would just say any other form of
weight is going to work the way isolate
is our bet for the best balance of
protein per calorie and value so why is
Wolverine's way Iceland our favorite way
isolate well apparently because the name
sounds like Wolverine but besides that
it is just a very good solid dedicated
weight isolate product like that I mean
you aren't paying a lot of extra money
for a lot of extra bells and whistles
110 calories per scoop you're getting 26
grams of protein for half a gram of fat
and two grams of carbohydrates and one
gram of sugar is very remarkable and
really high protein density this is 87
protein by weight for this chocolate
flavor here it's just like whey protein
isolate cocoa powder natural and
artificial flavor some xanthan gum which
is a thickener and stabilizer and
Sucralose which is a Splenda this is
sweetener right what you aren't getting
here is soy which a lot of people don't
like there's no lesser thin which a lot
of people don't like there's no gluten
either so in addition to being our best
way I slip overall we also needed the
best digesting and the reason for that
are peppering and protease those are in
the 10 milligram blend of digestive
enzymes you're going to get each scoop
but what's cool about this is there's
been some research suggesting that when
you add in enzymes to a protein powder
the amino acids from the protein get
into your bloodstream more quickly so
that's why this is our best digesting
one in addition to the fact that like
most weight isolates this is
unbelievably low in sugar and low in
lactose so folks with lactose
sensitivities are probably going to have
an easier time drinking it talk to your
doctor first lastly this is the best way
to isolate for muscle growth when
talking about that it is important to
note that muscle growth is largely from
your overall calories overall protein
carbohydrates workout regimen sleep and
so on but when it comes to picking a
protein powder it's not a bad idea to
pick one that has certain ingredients
that make it digest more effectively and
more completely so you're getting more
of the protein you're consuming so that
you can feed your starving hungry amino
acid thirsty muscles to help them build
and recover better after a workout so
we're a big fan of this enzymes are a
big fan of the fact that it is free from
a lot of extra extraneous ingredients
it's great product man sovereigns best
muscle growth best congesting and also
best overall next up we're going to talk
about the best way ice look on a budget
that is going to be some caged there
whey protein Islip that very
imaginatively named this is about a
dollar and 46 cents per serving whereas
a Wolverines is closer to two dollars
per serving so the Price Is Right on
these probably because it's not from
grass-fed cows but the thing with
grass-fed Dairy is the health benefits
of grass for dairy lie in the fat
content and whey isolate is practically
fat free so health-wise there's not a
difference really between grass-fed and
conventional whey there's a conventional
way but it's got a lot going for it it
has a tiny bit more carbohydrates as
well as three grams of carbs per 25
grams of protein as opposed to the two
grams of carbs 26 grams of protein and
Wolverine it's another reason why it's a
tiny bit cheaper but we're really just
kind of splitting hairs here this is
still very high in protein per calorie
and it's a really good pick if you're on
a budget we also named cage whey protein
isolate the best for athletes partly
because I mean athletes are often on a
budget but the main reason is that this
one unlike a lot of ways on the market
has been tested and satisfied by
informed spot so that means it's been
tested to make sure there's no banned
substances in this so Asia competitive
athlete that's usually a priority that
your supplements have a certification
from a group like informed sport so yeah
that's the best for athletes and also
fortunately the best on a budget as well
one more thing I forgot to say earlier
if you want to go through this
information that you're in Pace we have
a written version of this article so
that's helpful for a lot of folks if you
just want to Google bar band best way
isolate that'll bring it right up and uh
you'll be able to read all this and see
the pics and see the research we're
citing as well next up we're going to
talk about the best way I slip for
weight loss uh to be clear again weight
loss is about calories it's like weight
gain is right if you want to lose weight
you want to make sure that you're simply
getting fewer calories not too many
fewer calories than you burn in a day
over a longer period of time that said a
supplement like this one we think is
ideal for folks looking to lose weight
that is on its grass-fed where you
isolate this is a really high quality
supplement what's really interesting
here is it has a whole bunch of extra
ingredients right now that does raise
the price a little bit as mentioned
that's the trade-off you make with these
sorts of products but a few things you
should know about on its way I slit is
it's just 110 calories per scoop for a
nice dollar 21.1 grams of protein it's
also all natural the no artificial
flavors or sweetness and on top of that
this has a whole lot of digestive
enzymes as well in addition to that it
has a little bit of probiotic bacteria
to 2. the project per calorie is still
very high you're also getting a range of
digestive enzymes here you're getting
some probiotics from the lactobacillus
family and it's all natural and all of
these are reasons why we can say this
has to be a really really solid pick for
those who are looking to lose weight
plus it's the best tasting too it
doesn't have a whole range of flavors
which is like a little bit disappointing
but the flavors they do have are just
just absolutely delicious the chocolate
flavor as well is called mexican
chocolate and it's just the best
chocolate flavor it's got like a little
bit of cinnamon flavor in it so it
tastes a little bit more like a
chocolate cookie it's a bit hard to
explain taste like this but I can assure
you that while the price is a little
high out on it the product is very high
quality it's very all-natural and The
Taste is is second to none lastly we
want to talk about one of our favorite
supplement Brands which is transparent
Labs so transparent Labs they're known
for being very transparent right they
tell you all about their ingredients how
much of each ingredient they use where
they're from why they use it with
studies to back up all their claims a
really big fan of this brand and we
named it the best all-natural wave
potion I slip because it's totally all
natural so no artificial flavors no
sweeteners and they even produce like a
certificate of verification on this site
for people who are like very interested
in this kind of stuff so that is an
important one you even get the precise
amount of grams of each ingredient which
you're not going to get in any other
product here like when something says it
has Stevia and sodium chloride and
flavoring it's going to say it's 480
milligrams of natural flavoring it's 165
milligrams of stevia it's also very
delicious it's got eight different
flavors you can buy on this site and we
also think it's the best recovery partly
because it's just really high in protein
right this one has 28 grams of protein
for 120 calories and zero grams of fat
but on top of that this has some extra
sodium in it with a nice seven percent
of the recommended daily intake we
thought this made it a nice addition to
any athlete's recovery process so we
named this one the best all-natural and
the best for Recovery in the way I slip
game so that does it for our list of the
best way I slits on the market
um just to wrap up uh people often ask
what are the benefits of taking away
Islip right I touched on this earlier
but just to wrap up this video weight I
slip relative to a concentrate it has
more protein per calorie it is generally
lower if not entirely free of lactose
lower if entirely for your fat lower is
entirely free of carbohydrates so all
this means you're generally getting more
protein per gram and per calorie which
is important a lot of folks especially
trying to lose weight and you're really
tightly controlled diet in addition to
that whey is the most bioavailable
protein on Earth which means that it
absorbs the most effectively of any
protein out there better than meat
better than soy better than just about
anything so that's a really cool touch
as well and generally it's a good idea
to have a higher protein diet which way
isolate can help you to do right it is
linked to better body composition
meaning if you're consuming that much
protein you tend to have more muscle and
less body fat you also burn more
calories digesting protein it's very
very satiating which means that it is
better at curling your appetite and
you're less likely to overeat all of
these may sound a little bit aesthetic
to you but in addition to that having a
good ratio of body fat and muscle has a
wide range of health benefits associated
with it as well including things like
better bone density and better blood
pressure as well there's a ton of
studies on this I encourage you to check
them out but there's a lot of reasons to
take away isolate even if you're not a
competitive athlete so hopefully with
magic Ministry of that in today's video
remember if you want to learn more about
this kind of stuff and have a look at
some of the studies we've been talking
about and make your own way through the
research just give us a Google just go
to buy Robin Bestway Islip and the
article will come right up so thanks for
watching hope you learned something and
we'll see you in the next video
[Music]